SHAYNE MORGAN

Albany, Oregon 97321 | (541) 805-9785 | shayne.m.m@gmail.com

Professional Summary

Qualified Cyber security candidate and leader with management and sales experience. Strong technical and writing skills. Multi-media production capabilities in Print, Broadcast, and Internet. Strong Cyber security skills and attributes. Team player with zero drama. Well balanced and emotionally intelligent.

Skills

- Cybersecurity
- Adobe Cloud
- BurpSuite
- Metasploit
- Nmap

- Wireshark
- Microsoft Office 365
- OWASP Top 10
- Skilled researcher

Work History

Cyber Researcher 06/2019 to Current

Self-Employeed – Albany, Oregon

- Recommend improvements in security systems and procedures
- Conducted security audits to identify vulnerabilities
- Researched and developed new computer forensic tools
- Performed risk analyses to identify appropriate security countermeasures
- Developed plans to safeguard computer files against modification, destruction or disclosure
- Reviewed violations of computer security procedures and developed mitigation plans
- Monitored computer virus reports to determine when to update virus protection systems
- Encrypted data and erected firewalls to protect confidential information
- Adhered to rigorous standards for customer service, merchandising, operational safety and store security policies and guidelines
- Volunteered at local charity events, in addition to increased experience in social engagements and public speaking
- Consulted with internal and external clients via email and telephone correspondence to identify business needs and define technical requirements

Seasonal Tax Processor 04/2013 to Current

- Assisted in continuous improvement activities while developing and maintaining resulting documents
- Identified areas of weakness and recommended or implemented process improvements
- Collaborated with different departments and levels of management to gain consensus on procedural documentation
- Converted documents from one application to another, including cleaning, formatting and applying styles as needed
- Performed document reproduction, printing documents from electronic sources such as email attachments, PDF files, and cloud storage

Publisher 12/2010 to 12/2016

The Valley Explorer – Albany, Oregon

- Set overall vision and provided team leadership
- Reviewed and approved all contracts to clients prior to being submitted
- Modeled exceptional customer service and ensured associates understood direct link of revenue growth and customer loyalty cultivation techniques
- Performed design, layout, and typesetting of publications, office forms and various other projects to optimize designs and production strategies
- Provided analytical rationale to identify, develop and implement activities within allocated account base
- Understood each target customer's business model, mapped out organization and identified unique technology needs
- Recruited, hired and trained all staff, providing direct supervision, ongoing staff development and continuing education to employees
- Evaluated inventory and delivery needs, optimizing strategies to meet customer demands
- Demonstrated products and specific features at customer locations and special events
- Networked at events and by phone to expand business profits and revenues
- Performed cold-calling and follow-ups with leads to secure new revenue
- Grew business sales by 100% in 6 months through effective cross-selling, exceptional customer service and cold calling
- Devised and implemented product strategies for filling market gaps and driving consistent sales
- Developed and implemented sales strategies to increase revenue
- Boosted brand awareness, implemented promotional campaigns and employed sales tactics for The Valley Explorer
- Designed templates, headers and footers, multi-column documents, tables and charts for The
 Valley Explorers needs

Education

Butte High School - Butte, MT

Biology

Carroll College - Helena, MT

Associate of Arts: Networking And Cyber security

Chemeketa Community College - Salem, OR

Expected in 06/2020

Affiliations

- Member, OWASP Portland Chapter,
- ABC House volunteer and public speaker
- Oregon Cyber Security Council
- Member of The Corvallis Sustainability Coalition